skreened.com 2012-12-30

# Custom T-Shirts, Hoodies, Tees, Design a Tshirt. - Skreened

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We have created this privacy policy to make sure you know what information we collect and how we use it. By using the Skreened.com web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy.

###  Updates

From time to time, we may update this privacy policy. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by emailing you and/or placing a notice on our Website. Your continued use of the Skreened Website will be subject to the then current Privacy Policy.

###  But first, a note about uploading and posting information on the Skreened Website:

When you first open an account on Skreened , you will choose a _username_ and _password_. When you create a shop or gallery, comment on a design, or send a message on Skreened, your username is visible to other users.

Additionally, if your comment or message contains personal information and is posted by you in a page that is accessible to the public, third parties may make note of the information and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties as a result. Any content or information you upload is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy. Always use care when you post such information.

You may provide us with certain personally identifiable information when you:

  * register for a skreened account;
  * order products
  * request customer support or send us any other communication;
  * sign up for newsletters, email alerts, and special offers;
  * set up an affiliate account;
  * enter contests;
  * sign up for, or redeem, gift cards, codes, and special offers;

Such information may include your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, and credit card number. You may also provide us with information about other people, such as their email addresses, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Skreened Website or our promotions.

###  Information Collected by Cookies:

Skreened uses cookies, small text files on your computer which a website sends to your computer to allow the website to store information which uniquely identifies our users. Skreened's cookies do not collect or store personally identifiable information. Rather, the cookie stores a token which uniquely identifies a particular user at a particular time. That token is then linked to the user information in our secured databases. You can always reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to display a message when a cookie is being sent.

When you place orders or access your account information, we use commercially reasonable and generally-accepted technological safeguards to secure any information we collect about you. The secure server software (SSL) we use encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. In addition, your account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. You should always take steps to protect the confidentiality of the password you select.

We operate internationally and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States. As a result, your personal data will be processed by us in the United States where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with us, you agree to this privacy policy and you consent to the transfer of all information you provide to the United States.

**We use the personally identifiable information you provide to:**

  * provide the features and functionality of the Skreened Website;
  * fulfill your requests for our products and services;
  * pay commissions and affiliate payments;
  * communicate with you about the status of your orders and other inquiries about our products and services;
  * send you information about our products and services; and
  * provide notices about the results of contests, and other promotions.

We use your email address to communicate with you about your account and to send you certain notification emails. You can change the frequency of those emails in your Skreened account settings.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send marketing messages without your consent. Similarly, if you email a product to a friend or refer a friend to the Skreened Website or our promotions, we will use your friend's email to send them the e-mail you requested. You and your friend's e-mail addresses will only be used for this purpose unless permission is otherwise granted.

We may use non-personally identifiable information to monitor the use and performance of the SKREENED Website so that we can learn more about how people use the Skreened Website and improve our products and services.

Skreened does not share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your consent except that:

Skreened provides information to its agents and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes, such as: processing credit card transactions; communicating with customers; providing customer service; managing information on our behalf; and enhancing the Skreened Website features and functionality. In such cases, we require that these parties agree to use the information solely for the purpose for which we provided it to them and in accordance with our privacy policy.

Skreened may also release information (including your name, addresses, telephone number, and account activity) when we, in our sole discretion believe that such release is necessary or appropriate to:

  * comply with law;
  * comply with subpoenas, warrants, court orders, government investigations, or other legal process;
  * enforce or apply the terms of any of our user or license agreements;
  * investigate or respond to allegations of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other unlawful activity
  * investigate fraud or similar claims; or
  * protect the rights, property or safety of Skreened, our users, or others.

In the event that Skreened is acquired by, or merged with, another company, Skreened reserves the right to transfer all information we have collected from our users in connection with such acquisition or merger.

Skreened may disclose non-personally-identifiable information to third parties in aggregate form to potential business partners and investors.

###  **What about Children's Privacy?**

Children under the age of thirteen are allowed to upload graphics and images and to order products with their parent's consent. To order products, the child must indicate his or her age, submit his or her name and his or her mailing address and shipping address if different from the mailing address together with a valid credit card number. This is the only information collected from a child.

This information is used to fulfill the requested order; confirm shipment; complete record keeping including commission entitlements and pay affiliate fees, if any, and to advise the child concerning new Skreened products, services or policies.

Parents of children under the age of 13 have the option to consent to the collection of this information from their children or not. Such consent will not be used as consent for the dissemination of any of this information and the information will not be released by Skreened to third parties without the parents' consent except as may be required by law or upon court order.

Personal information at Skreened is kept confidential and is disclosed only with the consent of the Skreened user or as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We do not engage in the selling of the habits, behavior, buying patterns, or demographic information of our users. Skreened does not condition a child's participation in any on-line activity on the granting of any unnecessary information beyond that actually needed in connection with that activity.

Parents can review any information Skreened has received from a child and the parent can have that information deleted and the parent can forbid the collection of additional information from their child. If you want to review any information obtained from your child or if you want to have any information obtained from your child deleted from the Skreened records or to forbid any use of such information, simply [contact us](http://skreened.com/static/contact).

###  **How can I change, delete, or update my information?**

Most of your account information can be changed in the account section of the Skreened Website. If you have any questions about what information is stored, please contact us at [help@skreened.com](mailto:help@skreened.com).
